let MCQS = [{
    question: "What's_____ name? She is Sussy.",
    choice1: "A) my",
    choice2: "B) your",
    choice3: "C) his",
    choice4: "D) her",
    answer: 3
},
            {
                question: "Do you _____ cooking? Of course.",
    choice1: "A) to Like",
    choice2: "B) liked",
    choice3: "C) like",
    choice4: "D) will like",
    answer: 2
},
            {
                question: "My friends _____ from Germany.",
    choice1: "A) is",
    choice2: "B) are",
    choice3: "c) am",
    choice4: "D) isn't",
    answer: 1
},
            {
                question: "_____ do you exercise? I exercise twice a week",
    choice1: "A) What time",
    choice2: "B) Where",
    choice3: "C) How often",
    choice4: "D) Who",
    answer: 2
},
            {
                question: "Why _____ crying? ",
    choice1: "A) is she",
    choice2: "B) she was",
    choice3: "C) did she",
    choice4: "D) she is",
    answer: 0
},
            {
                question: "A car is _____ than a cell phone",
    choice1: "A) the most expensive",
    choice2: "B) expensive",
    choice3: "C) more expensive",
    choice4: "as expensive as",
    answer: 2
},          {
    question: "Anne _____ at home last night",
choice1: "A) isn't",
choice2: "B) didn't",
choice3: "C) weren't",
choice4: "D) wasn't",
answer: 3
},
{
    question: "  _____ you_____ Tv last night when I called you? What else ____ you do?",
choice1: "A) Are/watching/ do",
choice2: "B) Is/watching/do",
choice3: "C) Were/watching /did",
choice4: "D) Did/watch/did",
answer: 2
},
{
    question: "What did Estela use to do after school? She ______ every afternoon.",
choice1: "A) plays basketball",
choice2: "B) use to play basketball",
choice3: "C) Used to",
choice4: "D) used to play basketball",
answer: 3
},
{
question: "What did Estela use to do after school? She ______ every afternoon.",
choice1: "A) plays basketball",
choice2: "B) use to play basketball",
choice3: "C) Used to",
choice4: "D) used to play basketball",
answer: 3
}









];